<resources>
    <!-- Name of the app is the same as the Danish county "Odsherred". Only translate if translation exists -->
    <string name="app_name">Odsherred</string>

    <!-- Button name for opening map location -->
    <string name="open_location">Open Location</string>

    <!-- Names for the different categories -->
    <string name="restaurants">Cafés and Restaurants</string>
    <string name="art">Art</string>
    <string name="geo_park">Geo park</string>
    <string name="camping_sites">Camping sites</string>

    <!-- flavour text strings for Restaurents and cafés category -->
    <string-array name="restaurent_flavour_array">
        <item>Dragsholm Castle was acknowledged by the US food magazine Bon Appétit as one of the 11 best Food Lover’s Hotels outside the United States in 2014.\n\nAt Dragsholm Slot, we wish for the site\'s history and location to be seen as well as tasted. Our ambition for the castle\'s gourmet restaurant "Slotskøkkenet" is to belong to the Nordic gastronomic elite both in the present and in the future.\n\nSlotskøkkenet is an innovative gourmet cuisine. The basis is the castle\'s history and the seasonal produce from the Lammefjord and the rest of Odsherred which has strong roots in the Danish and Nordic food. This way, the past and the future are united on the plate.\n\nWine plays a very special role at Dragsholm Slot. The wine cellar contains a selection of excellent wines, discovered during visits with wine growers, on vineyards and through numerous wine tastings by some of the best wine merchants in the country.\n\nAdvance table reservation necessary.</item>
        <item>Come and enjoy the atmosphere in our café. We keep it simple and with a smile.\n\nHere you can relax and treat yourself to classic dishes, vegetarian soups and sweets. Everything homemade.\n\nOur priority is to make you feel at home and there is always time for a chat.</item>
        <item>New maritime café and gallery at Nykøbing Harbour with a large terrace facing the water.\n\nThe café offers sandwiches, salads, lunch platter etc.\n\nIn summer we serve brunch and occasional barbecue.\n\nFrom the classic takeaway we sell hotdogs, fries and burgers.\n\nLots of parking.</item>
        <item>Enjoy our freshly smoked herring, salmon burger,  the famous “Stjerneskud”, the coarsely chopped fish cakes or savour our “Tapas from fish and shellfish” not to mention the shellfish plate with ½ lobster, shrimps and crayfish.\n\nQuench your thirst with beer from Rørvig Bryghus, ice-cold white wine, local cider, organic juice or soft drink. Espresso and Café Latte, coffee and cake (brownies and muffins).\n\nEXPERIENCE THE ATMOSPHERE ON RØRVIG HARBOUR</item>
        <item>Hotel du Vest is a small charming hotel with own café, patio and shop, located in quiet surroundings in the old market town Nykøbing Sjælland. Hotel du Vest is the popular meeting place in town where you may enjoy homemade cake, freshly brewed coffee, brunch or the popular "Hotel du Vest Burger" with organic meat from the Hereford cattle of Twillingegården.</item>
        <item>Lyngkroen wants to be known as a fascinating eating place, engaged in developing the Danish cuisine. We cook and we love to eat, both with high quality produce.\n\nWe eat our way through the various seasons and enjoy the good produce back to basic.\n\nLive music during the summer.</item>
        <item>Madkunsten is a lovely restaurant, located in the middle of the pedestrian street in Nykøbing Sj.\n\nWe produce everything in our own kitchen and most of our ingredients are purchased locally by good farmers, meat producers and fruit growers.\n\nWe offer a  charming patio, a sidewalk café for those who want to enjoy the buzzling street life and a comfortable modern restaurant and shop where we sell our homemade bread etc. for "take-away"</item>
        <item>Freshly furnished restaurant and café in light rooms.\n\nFrench/Italian cuisine based on the season\'s fresh ingredients.\n\nWe offer:\nLight lunch dishes.\nSandwich, coffee &amp; cake.\nRestaurant with à la carte menu.</item>
        <item>Authentic atmosphere and not least love for food and guests.</item>
        <item>Cheerful cafe/restaurant on the pedestrian Street in Nykøbing Sjælland.\nExtensive, varied menu. Specialities include pizza, pasta and steaks.\n\nOpening hours: 10am till 10pm\nSpecial lunch menu from 11am till 4pm.\nTake away and deliveries until 10pm.\n\nWe have separate reception rooms.</item>
        <item>The most delightful cafe in town. Extensive menu with many specialities. Come and savour a delicious brunch, pizza, sandwich or meat dish. Enjoy our food in tasteful surroundings.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- flavour text strings for Art category -->
    <string-array name="art_flavour_array">
        <item>Art from Odsherred through times with special focus on landscape paintings. The essence of the collection is the generation of Odsherred Painters from the 1930s, who focused on Odsherred.\n\nThe Odsherred Art Museum lies in the heart of scenic Odsherred in the "white house" in Asnæs. It is one of the most remarkable and most beautiful buildings in the town, and the light rooms are perfectly suitable for art exhibitions.</item>
        <item>An interestin glass gallery with own works as well as bronze art from Athens, raku-burnt from Skagen and local silver jewels design. Always new and surprising items. Also open as per appointment.</item>
        <item>The extension of Algade towards Rørvig is named Lindeallé.\n\nHere Birgit Krogh lives and works with small and big unique specimen, sculptures, reliefs, vases, bowls and plates.\n\nIn many of her works you are met with a fertile narrative joy which embraces and celebrates life in its entire being. In a very attentive manner she sets figures, stories and thoughts in motion.\n\nTile tables and kitchens tiles to order.</item>
        <item>Beautifully located studio with exhibition of acrylic paintings and sculptures in papier maché.\n\nPaintings expressed in strong colours through a dialogue between recognizable symbols and playful abstractions.</item>
        <item>Ceramic gallery and boutique with:\nDesign, porcelain, stoneware and faience.\nUnique objects.\nReliefs.\nSculptures.\nDecoration works.\n\nThe exhibition also includes wall sheets and models from the decoration works, among these churches and architecture.\n\nOpen from Whitsun to September 1. Rest of the year open as per agreement.\nAdmission: Free</item>
        <item>Workshop with exhibition of: Unique specimen, articles for everyday use in glass, pottery and slate tables and a new grand selection of glass figurines\n\nOur aim is to design and produce Danish handicraft at reasonable prices.\n\nAlso open as by agreement.</item>
        <item>A relaxed and experimental exhibition venue presenting contemporary artists from the young to the established. 10\-12 artists take part in the summer exhibition.\n\nYou can expect to see many different styles, such as figurative with a touch of humour. We highly value the artistic quality, commitment and content.\n\nThe gallery is located on the peninsula of Nakke Hage in scenic surroundings. We take pleasure in informing and advising you about purchase of art.</item>
        <item>Gallery of 228m2 witrh a view of Sidinge Fjord and Grevinge Forest.\n\nDuring the summer months, various guest exhibitors display paintings in oil and acrylics, jewellery, felt works, woodcuts and sculptures in stone and clay as well as unique specimen in wood.\n\nDuring opening hours, one of the artists will be present.\n\nVisits outside the official opening hours as per agreement with Bjarne Wyrwik.\n\nOpening hours are also valid during holidays.\n\nFree admittance.\nPublic bus right outside.\nPossibility for access in a wheelchair.\nPossibility  to buy refreshments.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- flavour text strings for geo park category -->
    <string-array name="geo_flavour_array" >
        <item>Esterhøj is situated on an ancient Bronze Age burial mound (89 metres above sea level). On the burial mound the Reunion Stone can be seen. </item>
        <item>Kongsøre Forrest on the Isefjord has an incredibly rich collection of ancient monuments. The long dolmen barrow of King Øres Graves lies in the heart of the soutern part of the wood and consists of af single chamber that has been provided with a new capstone after the dolmen was restored i 1937.\n\nThe chamber is rectangular, about 1,5 metres long and 1 metre wide. At the foot of the chamber is a circle of 35 large stones. On one of these stones there are shell-shaped depressions.\n\nThe burial chamber was plundered in ancient times, though legend has it that "a golden chain long enough to stretch from the grave to Stokkeberg" (several kilometres away!) still lies in the grave.</item>
        <item>It was built in the year 1240 and it existed in 100 years until it was destroyed in an attack on some people from Holstein who lived in the castle.\n\nAfter it was destroyed King Valdemar decided not to rebuild the castle and instead he used the materials for building a nearby farm.</item>
        <item>In 1807 fieldworks for ships, which sailed into the creek, were built. The creek has been used as a war harbour for centuries - it was also used as a war harbour before the fieldworks were built.</item>
        <item>The village of Ulkerup was established about the year 1300. It was owned by the king and the farmers had to pay annual taxes for the right of using soil.\n\nIn the years 1750 to 1760 the terrible cattle plague raged and the farmers suffered great losses. In 1782 the king decided to close the village because of the bad financial circumstances.\n\nThe village is situated in the middle of Ulkerup Forest and the area makes a total of 4 hectare.</item>
        <item>The Bronze Age burial mound Vejrhøj is situated 121 meter above sea level and is thereby Zealands third highest point. Vejrhøj gives name to the Vejrhøj Arch, which was created during the Ice Age about 15.000 years ago.\n\nSeveral monuments of antiquity are found on the Vejrhøj Arch, including Esterhøj, Maglehøj and Dutterhøje.\n\nOn a clear day 27 churches can be seen from the top of Vejrhøj, including the cathedral in Roskilde.\n\nFrom the parking place you can walk the 900 metres to Vejrhøj through Vejrhøj Forest. The path through the forest is marked.</item>
        <item>In the small village of Kelstrup cloe to Vig, you find the very well preserved remains of a stone castle from the 14th century, the Kelstrup ruin. The ruin was protected in 1810 but was not properly researched until 2004.</item>
        <item>Birkehøj Passage Graves by Nyrup contain the longest burial chamber on Sealand ( 11m - 2m - 2m), constructed 5200 years ago. Visible from the main road and easily accessible.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- flavour text strings for Camping sites category -->
    <string-array name="camping_flavour_array">
        <item>Sanddobbernes Camping is located by road 225 between Salgelse and Nykøbing Sj., only 1 hour\'s drive from Copenhagen.\n\nThe area is of great natural beauty between dunes and directly by a sandy and child-friendly beach at Nekselø Bay with a view of Nekselø and Sejerø, 3,5 kms from Dragsholm Golf Club.\n\n- a family oriented camping site\n- good activity possibilities\n- mini golf\n- close to Dragsholm Castle\n- very suitable for the disabled\n- possible to rent caravans and camping chalets\n\nThere are also bouncers and moon cars.</item>
        <item>The camping site is situated in beautiful nature with mixed growth which divides the camping site into a maze of snug corners. Very fine sanitary conditions.\n\nOnly 200 m from one of the finest sandy beaches in Denmark. The site is quiet and very suited for children.\n\nPossible to rent chalets and campers.\n\nShort walk to Nykøbing Sj. (only 2 km). Nykøbing Sj. has a pedestrian street with many shops and cafés which has created many good holiday experiences for thousands of tourists.</item>
        <item>3* child friendly site with own acces to the finest sand beach. Good playground, boucers, petanque, hotspot fitness centre and bicycle rental. The site is surrounded by coniferous woodland. 2,5 km from Nykøbing Sj. and close to the ferry to Hundested and good public transport. The area offers a rich variety of activities. 3 nice family rooms.</item>
        <item>Høve Camping is the oldest camping site in Denmark, located in Høve Forest right by the Sejeroe Bay and its lovely beach.\n\n*Only for tents\n*New bathing and toilet facilities\n*Washing machine\n*300 meters to a restaurant\n*5 villa tents for 4 persons - fully equipped - to let\n* No cars allowed on the camping site</item>
        <item>Beautifully situated at Isefjord and Kongsøre forest.\n\nWe offer:\n- Modern facilities\n- Swimming pool\n- Restaurant right next to site\n- Playground with bouncer\n- Crazy golf\n- Dogs on a leash allowed.\n- Singlecamp</item>
        <item>Teglværksgårdens Camping is located by the scenic Sejerø Bay.\n\nEvery site of apprx. 100 m2 with private electric meter for the caravans.\n\nThe camping site is well sheltered.\n\nToilets for disabled and modern bathrooms.\n\n2 chalets for 2 persons and 1 chalet for 4 persons.\n\nOpening periods 2011: 1/1 \- 31/12</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
